{
    "by": "大大大 chotto crazy 2020 MAX",
    "types": [
        {
            "id": "shokoyamamura",
            "title": "ラ",
            "name": "Shoko Yamamura",
            "message": "Well, would you like to listen to it?<br>まずは聴いてみませんか",
            "url": true
        },
        {
            "id": "jackdoe",
            "title": "曲",
            "name": "Jackdoe",
            "message": "Your dreams will not come true when you give it up, I believe.<br>きっとあなたの夢はいつか叶います。",
            "url": true
        },
        {
            "id": "sou",
            "title": "藍",
            "name": "Sou",
            "message": "this is all about after all, ...what conjunction would you choose after this sentence?<br>「所詮〇〇なんてこんなもの」この言葉のあとに、あなたはどんな言葉を続けますか？",
            "url": true
        },
        {
            "id": "weather",
            "title": "天",
            "name": "Shoji Funakawa",
            "message": "Do you think the weather tomorrow is?<br>明日はいい天気だと思う？"
        },
        {
            "id": "chishima",
            "title": "千",
            "name": "Chishima Foundation for Creative Osaka",
            "message": "北加賀屋を拠点に、大阪やその周辺で活動するアーティスト、クリエイター、また彼らを支える人たちの活動を支援する事業を行っています。",
            "url": true
        }
    ],
    "questions": [
        {
            "id": "Q1",
            "question": "Are you enjoying your life?",
            "jp": "いくぞ、1.2.3.ダー！人生、楽しんでますかー？",
            "yes": "yes",
            "left": "はい",
            "no": "no",
            "right": "いいえ",
            "left_to": "Q3",
            "light_to": "Q2"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q2",
            "question": "Do you have a belief?",
            "jp": "誰に言われても曲げることのない信念がある",
            "yes": "yes",
            "left": "ある",
            "no": "no i don't",
            "right": "ない",
            "left_to": "Q7",
            "light_to": "Q4"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q3",
            "question": "With who?",
            "jp": "誰と？",
            "yes": "someone you know",
            "left": "知っている人",
            "no": "someone you don't know",
            "right": "知らない人",
            "left_to": "Q5",
            "light_to": "Q6"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q4",
            "question": "Shine",
            "jp": "ひかる",
            "yes": "bright",
            "left": "まぶしい",
            "no": "indistinct",
            "right": "よくみえない",
            "left_to": "Q7",
            "light_to": "Q8"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q5",
            "question": "You wear your shoes first from",
            "jp": "靴を履くのは",
            "yes": "right",
            "left": "右から",
            "no": "left",
            "right": "左から",
            "left_to": "Q7",
            "light_to": "Q11"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q6",
            "question": "Did you take train to get here today?",
            "jp": "今日は電車に乗ってきた",
            "yes": "yes",
            "left": "はい",
            "no": "no",
            "right": "いいえ",
            "left_to": "Q8",
            "light_to": "Q5"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q7",
            "question": "Blow",
            "jp": "ふく",
            "yes": "far ahead",
            "left": "とおくへ",
            "no": "in here",
            "right": "ここで",
            "left_to": "Q13",
            "light_to": "Q9"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q8",
            "question": "How much?",
            "jp": "どれくらい？",
            "yes": "pretty much",
            "left": "けっこう",
            "no": "just a little",
            "right": "ちょっと",
            "left_to": "Q10",
            "light_to": "Q9"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q9",
            "question": "When do you relax more?",
            "jp": "一人でいるときと誰かといるとき、どっちが落ち着く？",
            "yes": "alone",
            "left": "一人",
            "no": "with someone",
            "right": "誰かといるとき",
            "left_to": "Q12",
            "light_to": "Q10"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q10",
            "question": "Want to syncronize?",
            "jp": "合わせる？",
            "yes": "yes",
            "left": "はい",
            "no": "no",
            "right": "いいえ",
            "left_to": "Q11",
            "light_to": "Q12"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q11",
            "question": "Are you glad when someone tells you that you are a good person?",
            "jp": "「あなた良い人だね」って言われると素直にうれしいですか？",
            "yes": "yes",
            "left": "それほどでも~。と照れる",
            "no": "no",
            "right": "むしろ、相手を疑ってしまう。",
            "left_to": "Q14",
            "light_to": "Q15"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q12",
            "question": "Do you like yourself?",
            "jp": "自分のことが好きかどうか",
            "yes": "yes",
            "left": "好き",
            "no": "no i don't like myself",
            "right": "嫌い",
            "left_to": "Q13",
            "light_to": "Q17"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q13",
            "question": "Heap up",
            "jp": "つもる",
            "yes": "being buried",
            "left": "埋まる",
            "no": "melt in mouse",
            "right": "口で溶ける",
            "left_to": "Q14",
            "light_to": "Q16"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q14",
            "question": "Do you know the taste that feel like a smell of something?",
            "jp": "〇〇の匂いのような味を知ってる？",
            "yes": "Yes",
            "left": "はい",
            "no": "No",
            "right": "いいえ",
            "left_to": "Q18",
            "light_to": "Q15"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q15",
            "question": "Which do you think is more interesting if they are colored?",
            "jp": "色がついていたらおもしろいと思うのは",
            "yes": "rain",
            "left": "雨",
            "no": "tear",
            "right": "涙",
            "left_to": "Q17",
            "light_to": "Q16"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q16",
            "question": "Being exposed",
            "jp": "うたれる",
            "yes": "run down on my cheek",
            "left": "頬を伝う",
            "no": "hold an umbrella",
            "right": "傘をさす",
            "left_to": "Q21",
            "light_to": "Q20"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q17",
            "question": "Are you angry at something?",
            "jp": "今、何かに、怒ってますか？",
            "yes": "yes",
            "left": "世の中に対し、もの申したいことが沢山ある！",
            "no": "no",
            "right": "何事もなるようになるさ。",
            "left_to": "Q19",
            "light_to": "Q24"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q18",
            "question": "A word is",
            "jp": "言葉は",
            "yes": "music",
            "left": "音楽",
            "no": "a symbol",
            "right": "記号",
            "left_to": "Q23",
            "light_to": "Q22"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q19",
            "question": "Do you feel you are watched over by someone?",
            "jp": "自分は誰かに守られていると感じている？",
            "yes": "yes / maybe yes",
            "left": "感じるている、もしくは感じる時がある",
            "no": "no i don't",
            "right": "特に感じない",
            "left_to": "Q23",
            "light_to": "Q22"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q20",
            "question": "Do you want to meet yourself in 20 years?",
            "jp": "20年後の自分に会いたいと思いますか？",
            "yes": "yes",
            "left": "はい",
            "no": "no",
            "right": "いいえ",
            "left_to": "Q18",
            "light_to": "Q21"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q21",
            "question": "For camping you'd go to",
            "jp": "キャンプをするなら",
            "yes": "the mountain",
            "left": "山",
            "no": "the beach",
            "right": "海",
            "left_to": "Q26",
            "light_to": "Q25"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q22",
            "question": "Which do you like?",
            "jp": "夏と冬どっちが好き？",
            "yes": "summer",
            "left": "夏",
            "no": "winter",
            "right": "冬",
            "left_to": "Q24",
            "light_to": "Q24"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q23",
            "question": "You would sing",
            "jp": "歌うなら？",
            "yes": "with someone",
            "left": "誰かと",
            "no": "a solo",
            "right": "ひとりで",
            "left_to": "Q30",
            "light_to": "Q25"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q24",
            "question": "Getting first place is all about?",
            "jp": "一番でなければ意味は無いですか？",
            "yes": "yes",
            "left": "勝つと言うことは、そういう事だ。",
            "no": "no",
            "right": "何事も腹八分目がちょうど良い。",
            "left_to": "Q28",
            "light_to": "Q27"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q25",
            "question": "Hold up",
            "jp": "かざす",
            "yes": "cold",
            "left": "つめたい",
            "no": "warm",
            "right": "あたたかい",
            "left_to": "Q29",
            "light_to": "Q26"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q26",
            "question": "You prefer Hotcake to pancake?",
            "jp": "パンケーキよりホットケーキが好きだ",
            "yes": "yes",
            "left": "はい",
            "no": "no",
            "right": "いいえ",
            "left_to": "Q34",
            "light_to": "Q27"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q27",
            "question": "Do you want to appear on TV program or some media and being said <b>you are weird</b> by celebrity?",
            "jp": "TVとかに出演して、マ〇コデラックスに「あんた、変態ねぇ。」と言われてみたいですか？",
            "yes": "yes",
            "left": "目指せ香川〇之、さ〇なクン！",
            "no": "no",
            "right": "そもそも、TVに出るなんてありえない。",
            "left_to": "Q32",
            "light_to": "Q28"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q28",
            "question": "Do you think youself are an &quot;adult&quot;?",
            "jp": "自分を「大人」だと思っている？",
            "yes": "no i am still a child",
            "left": "まだ子どもだと思っている",
            "no": "yes i think i am an adult",
            "right": "大人だと思っている",
            "left_to": "Q31",
            "light_to": "Q29"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q29",
            "question": "Being hit",
            "jp": "あたる",
            "yes": "burn",
            "left": "燃える",
            "no": "spark",
            "right": "萌える",
            "left_to": "Q31",
            "light_to": "Q35"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q30",
            "question": "Do you know a gentle song for the world?",
            "jp": "世界のための優しい音楽を知ってる？",
            "yes": "yes",
            "left": "はい",
            "no": "no",
            "right": "いいえ",
            "left_to": "Q32",
            "light_to": "Q33"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q31",
            "question": "Are you happy now?",
            "jp": "今、幸せですか？",
            "yes": "I would rather say yes",
            "left": "どちらかといえば幸せ",
            "no": "I would rather say no",
            "right": "どちらかといえば不幸",
            "left_to": "Q32",
            "light_to": "Q36"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q32",
            "question": "Do you like a sound?",
            "jp": "音は？",
            "yes": "yes",
            "left": "好き",
            "no": "no i don't",
            "right": "嫌い",
            "left_to": "Q34",
            "light_to": "Q33"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q33",
            "question": "Do you have any hobbies that make you get too crazy in it?",
            "jp": "エモ過ぎて、鼻血を出してまう(もしくは、それに近い気分)になるくらいの趣味はありますか？",
            "yes": "yes",
            "left": "それくらいの「推し」がいる。",
            "no": "no",
            "right": "そもそも、そういう類の人が理解できない。",
            "left_to": "Q36",
            "light_to": "Q37"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q34",
            "question": "Tomato should be eaten with salt",
            "jp": "トマトに塩は",
            "yes": "yes",
            "left": "いる",
            "no": "no",
            "right": "いらない",
            "left_to": "Q38",
            "light_to": "Q43"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q35",
            "question": "Being covered",
            "jp": "おおわれる",
            "yes": "cool",
            "left": "涼しい",
            "no": "look out over",
            "right": "見渡す",
            "left_to": "Q36",
            "light_to": "Q37"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q36",
            "question": "Do you think you would love things that you love now if you reborn?",
            "jp": "自分が好きなものを生まれ変わっても好きになる？",
            "yes": "I would definitely love them",
            "left": "絶対に好きになる",
            "no": "I might not love them",
            "right": "ならないかもしれない",
            "left_to": "Q40",
            "light_to": "Q37"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q37",
            "question": "When your opinion is different from others do you accept it?",
            "jp": "人と考えが違った時、そんな考えも有りかもと受け容れられますか？",
            "yes": "yes",
            "left": "自分の考えが必ずしも、総てでは無い。",
            "no": "no",
            "right": "時と場合には、押し通す！",
            "left_to": "Q39",
            "light_to": "Q41"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q38",
            "question": "Do you often go to 100yen shop?",
            "jp": "100均にはよく行きますか",
            "yes": "yes",
            "left": "はい",
            "no": "no",
            "right": "いいえ",
            "left_to": "Q43",
            "light_to": "Q42"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q39",
            "question": "Do you think there is something when you exceed the limit?",
            "jp": "限界の向こう側は有ると思いますか？",
            "yes": "yes",
            "left": "できることなら、見てみたい。",
            "no": "no",
            "right": "人それぞれには、できることとできないことがある。",
            "left_to": "Q44",
            "light_to": "Q42"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q40",
            "question": "What would you do if you found a person in trouble?",
            "jp": "困ってる人がいたらどうする？",
            "yes": "would help her/him",
            "left": "助ける",
            "no": "would do nothing",
            "right": "何もしない",
            "left_to": "Q44",
            "light_to": "Q38"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q41",
            "question": "Strain",
            "jp": "そばだてる",
            "yes": "fall",
            "left": "ふる",
            "no": "stopped",
            "right": "やんでいる",
            "left_to": "Q42",
            "light_to": "Q45"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q42",
            "question": "Which do you want it wider in your room?",
            "jp": "ワンルームマンションで広かったらうれしいのは",
            "yes": "kitchen",
            "left": "キッチン",
            "no": "balcony",
            "right": "ベランダ",
            "left_to": "Q43",
            "light_to": "Q46"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q43",
            "question": "You can recognize musical scale &quot;Ra&quot;",
            "jp": "「ラ」の音がわかる",
            "yes": "yes",
            "left": "はい",
            "no": "no",
            "right": "いいえ",
            "left_to": "Q46",
            "light_to": "Q49"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q44",
            "question": "Do you think your meal is good as usual?",
            "jp": "今日も、ご飯(もしくはパンはたまたナン)は、おいしいですか？",
            "yes": "yes",
            "left": "あと、味噌汁と魚があれば良い",
            "no": "no",
            "right": "いいえ",
            "left_to": "Q50",
            "light_to": "Q47"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q45",
            "question": "Get wet",
            "jp": "ぬれる",
            "yes": "heavy",
            "left": "おもい",
            "no": "light",
            "right": "かるい",
            "left_to": "Q47",
            "light_to": "Q48"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q46",
            "question": "Which is round?",
            "jp": "丸いのはどっち",
            "yes": "a ballon",
            "left": "ふうせん",
            "no": "a cat",
            "right": "ねこ",
            "left_to": "chishima",
            "light_to": "weather"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q47",
            "question": "Do you think there is a thing that more important than a life?",
            "jp": "命よりも大切ななにかがある",
            "yes": "yes",
            "left": "ある",
            "no": "no i don't",
            "right": "ない",
            "left_to": "jackdoe",
            "light_to": "sou"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q48",
            "question": "Weathering with ...",
            "jp": "天気と共に",
            "yes": "in here",
            "left": "ここで",
            "no": "somewhere",
            "right": "どこかで",
            "left_to": "weather",
            "light_to": "shokoyamamura"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q49",
            "question": "Would you like to listen to it?",
            "jp": "聴いてみる？",
            "yes": "yeah",
            "left": "いいよ",
            "no": "well. maybe...",
            "right": "どうだろう",
            "left_to": "shokoyamamura",
            "light_to": "jackdoe"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q50",
            "question": "Why are you and I are asking questions like this?",
            "jp": "なぜ、あなたと私は、今、こうして、質問し合っているのでしょうか？",
            "yes": "because of this project",
            "left": "例1) このプロジェクトがあったから。",
            "no": "it is god only knows",
            "right": "例2) それは、神のみぞが知るコトさ。",
            "left_to": "sou",
            "light_to": "chishima"
        }
    ]
}